(Howard:)Oh, I love a good blitz,
especially with sour cream.
(Howard:)Get it?
Because it sounds like "blintz."
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Did someone say blintz?
(Leonard:)I just don't understand
(Leonard:)why you invited him here today.
(Penny:)Because you wouldn't
shut up about it.
(Penny:)When I called him,
he had nothing to do,
(Penny:)so I just thought it would--
(Raj:)Hey, guys, I'm trying
to cock in here.
(Penny:)Oh, sorry.
We'll keep it down.
(Raj:)No, no, speak up.
(Raj:)I'm about to use the blender,
(Raj:)and I don't want to miss anything.
(Leonard:)Well, you might have
to cock for one more
(Leonard:)because she invited Zack.
(Together:)What?
What?
(Raj:)My, my.
(Raj:)The plot, like my gravy, thickens.
(Sheldon:)I don't care for your
mother's bathroom.
(Sheldon:)There's not an angle
to do one's business
(Sheldon:)without a clown figurine
staring at you.
(Howard:)-That's why I sit.
-Yeah, that's why.